{
    "subject": "resource/Wilhelm-Ferdinand_Galland",
    "predicate": "ontology/relation",
    "object": "resource/Adolf_Galland",
    "human_readable": "Wilhelm Ferdinand Galland is related to Adolf Galland.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9864930510520935,
            "question": "Are Wilhelm Ferdinand Galland and Adolf Galland related?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9812535643577576,
            "question": "Is there a family connection between Wilhelm Ferdinand Galland and Adolf Galland?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9717267751693726,
            "question": "Who is Wilhelm Ferdinand Galland related to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9670170545578003,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Wilhelm Ferdinand Galland and Adolf Galland?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9530667662620544,
            "question": "What is the nature of the relationship between Wilhelm Ferdinand Galland and Adolf Galland?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9439133405685425,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the familial ties between Wilhelm Ferdinand Galland and Adolf Galland?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9371311068534851,
            "question": "Is there a family history shared by Wilhelm Ferdinand Galland and Adolf Galland?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9334668517112732,
            "question": "What type of connection exists between Wilhelm Ferdinand Galland and Adolf Galland?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9161684513092041,
            "question": "How are Wilhelm Ferdinand Galland and Adolf Galland connected?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7159116268157959,
            "question": "Do Wilhelm Ferdinand Galland and Adolf Galland share any familial bonds?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Wilhelm Ferdinand Galland is related to Adolf Galland.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6033_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How are Wilhelm Ferdinand Galland and Adolf Galland connected?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6033_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of connection exists between Wilhelm Ferdinand Galland and Adolf Galland?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6033_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a family history shared by Wilhelm Ferdinand Galland and Adolf Galland?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6033_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6033_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6033_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6033_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6033_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6033_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6033_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6033_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6033_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6033_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6033_67.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents contain information about Wilhelm-Ferdinand Galland and Adolf Galland, mentioning that they are brothers. Specifically, document `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6033/re-ranker-msmarco/18.txt` states:\n\n\"Wilhelm-Ferdinand was one of four Galland brothers to serve in the Luftwaffe.\"\n\nDocument `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6033/re-ranker-msmarco/52.txt` further confirms this relationship by mentioning Wilhelm-Ferdinand as one of Adolf's older brothers.\n\nTherefore, based on the information provided in the documents, it is correct to conclude that Wilhelm Ferdinand Galland is related to Adolf Galland."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the relationship between Wilhelm Ferdinand Galland and Adolf Galland. Specifically, they mention that both brothers served in the Luftwaffe and that Adolf Galland was Wilhelm Ferdinand's older brother."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}